(Sheldon:)Hmm.
(Sheldon:)What are you doing now?
(Raj:)Still making sure
the telescope's camera
(Raj:)is white-field balanced.
Oh, I see.
(Sheldon:)How about now?
(Raj:)Now I'm making sure
the telescope's camera
(Raj:)is white-field balanced and
wishing you had a coloring book.
(Sheldon:)Well, I can be helpful.
(Sheldon:)Give me something to do.
(Sheldon:)You know, my father
took me to work once,
(Sheldon:)and in ten minutes
I figured out
(Sheldon:)who'd been stealing
from the cash register.
(Sheldon:)It was my father.
(Sheldon:)Yeah, Dad lost his job,
(Sheldon:)but Mr. Hinckley
gave me a Fudgsicle.
(Raj:)Fine, you want
something to do?
(Raj:)There's about six months
of data on this hard drive.
(Raj:)Why don't you go through it
and see if you can spot
(Raj:)any patterns or anomalies.
(Sheldon:)Yep, I'm on it.
Hey, look at that!
(Sheldon:)An Indian guy outsourcing
a computer job to a white fella.
(Raj:)Yeah, okay,
whatever it takes
(Raj:)to keep you busy
for a few hours.
(Sheldon:)Found one.